So, day in the life. I haven't done one
of these in like 2 years. And a lot of
things have changed except my morning
routine. It's all the same thing. I
pretty much wake up 7:00 7:30 in the
morning. I brush my teeth and then I go
straight to the office. So, that's where
things have changed. So, we'll talk
about that when we get there. Right now,
for now, just brush my teeth. Sometimes
I shower, but I usually do the cold
plunge and all. You guys are going to
know all about that.
[Music]
Pretty much straight from waking up
right into the office. So, I don't do
the whole meditating. I don't do the
whole reading a book in the morning. I
don't drink coffee. I don't light a
candle, a candle, whatever. I don't do
any of that stuff. I don't know. I feel
like that's all superstitious. I am
superstitious for some stuff. But for me
to go trade, I just wake up in the
morning and I just come straight to
trade. Like this is where I have the
most clarity. Feel like if I have to do
a bunch of stuff in order to prepare
myself for trading, I almost like
putting pressure on myself that I have
to trade. If I just wake up, I come
here. There's nothing. I just leave.
There's no trading opportunity. I simply
don't take it. So I pretty much come
here. I get on my other phone that I
have here. Pretty much sleeps here all
the time where I answer all the Discord
messages with all the students cuz we're
about to start trading right now because
it is about 8:00 in the morning. So,
this is where I trade with all of my
students in the morning. I'll answer
Discord messages. I'll answer DMs. I'll
pretty much just engage with everybody
as much as I can and just focus on my
trading till about 11:30, 11:45 in the
morning. And then I just honestly after
that just take a nap because obviously I
trade London as well. I'm still doing
that from last time. So, the last time
that I did a day in the life I said I
hope that I'm not trading London and New
York at the same time. Yeah, I'm still
kind of doing that right now. So, we
pretty much usually take a nap today,
but for this video, we're gonna stay up.
And I also have Eric, which where he's
gonna come give me a haircut. We're
looking crazy. So, right now, for the
next about 3 to maybe 4 hours, I'm just
here inside the office. I don't leave at
all. I have a mini fridge right there
where I have all of my water, which it's
empty right now because we drank all the
water, but I don't leave to eat. I don't
do anything. Everything that I need is
in here. I have a bathroom over there.
So, pretty much I just focus and
centered inside of here. And then right
around maybe 12:31 is where I'll
actually eat. So, I do fast every single
day and that's been helping me a lot.
So, right now, we're just going to
trade, chill for a little bit, and uh
catch up with you guys.
[Music]
So, about like 4 hours later, bro, I I
used to have a gaming chair as my office
chair, and I got this big fat office,
but it's the best thing I could ever do.
I can sit here for hours. This thing is
comfortable. If you have one of those
gaming chairs, they are not comfortable.
They start hurting your ass. But as we
were doing the videos where I realized
some of the things from here are like
from the other like day in the life. So,
I don't know if you guys know who this
guy is, but this is the goat. Every
single time I'd win a trade, I used to
Yeah, this guy's been through a lot. If
you notice, he doesn't have ears. His
ears have pretty much been ripped off.
Um, and then this timer right here, this
timer is actually very essential because
I used to time all of my tasks. So, I
would have this pretty much right here.
And let's say that I was going to answer
DMs, for example, or I was going to
reply to Discord messages. I'm like,
"All right, I'm only going to do that
for 15 minutes. I don't have any other
distractions." And I put it here and I
time myself. I don't really use it
anymore because I have a very wellout
routine and I've been doing it for, you
know, 2 years already, so I don't really
need it. But if you are a beginner
person and you want to have something to
help you focus on your task, time
yourself. If you're going to say, "Okay,
I'm going to study trading." Put a
little timer. this costs $10 on Amazon.
Put a timer and be like, "All right, I'm
only going to study for an hour." And
then you put it right here. You're going
to notice within that hour that you're
about 15 minutes in and you're going to
have an urge of getting on Instagram or
you're going to have an urge of doing
something else. And you're going to
notice that your attention span and your
the way you focus is pretty much limp to
none. So, by you timing yourself, you
notice how much effort and time you
actually put into stuff. So, right now
it's exactly Oh, look. We're right on
right on time. 11:45. So, right now is
where I would literally get up from here
and take a nap. And I'm, you know,
usually tired. Not tired today. Haven't
drank anything other than water. But I
know Eric is pulling up. So, we're going
to get a quick haircut and then we'll I
know we have to go see the boat cuz we
put some new speakers on the boat and
then we have to go eat. And then after
eat, I know Jordan I think he wants to
go do something. So, for now, we just
chill until we after we get the haircut.
Let's go get haircut. So, last time you
guys saw this video, I had a goat. I
used to have a goat. Now I have a cat.
Hey,
you saw that? It actually responds. Have
you ever seen a cat that that responds?
Yeah, my cat. My cat [__] listens to
me. Oh, and I I wanted to show you guys.
This is one of my studios. I have four
inside this house. And pretty much I
just decided Yeah, bro. I just realized
I have like eight rooms in this [__]
house, bro. So, this is one of them. The
other ones I can't show you guys cuz
they're like my private rooms where, you
know, I like to Sounds like I have like
a porn room, bro. Why did I sound like
that? But they're my rooms that I just
use for certain. How do I come back from
the way I worded that [__] The what I
The point is that this is the famous
YouTube studio room. I even [__] put
a fireplace in this. Look at this. This
over here.
That [__] was $10,000. And it doesn't
even heat up, but it looks nice. So
yeah, this is the famous studio. How do
I come back from what I said?
All
right. So, we got Eric here.
Yo, this is not planned. This guy didn't
know we were doing this video. Check it.
Was it planned or no? No, it wasn't. It
wasn't. Right now, we got a haircut.
This guy always [__] me up. I'm loyal
on my people, bro.
You too much [__]
Eric's been cutting my hair for like
what, bro? Like six, seven years. Yeah,
like six, seven years for sure. And
things have changed, bro.
[__] changed. They're going crazy.
So, this guy's been [__] up my hair
for six to seven years, bro. No, I'm
kidding. These days, by the way, you
guys are seeing this is after I stre the
Super Bowl. We just got out of jail like
2 days ago, so like free now. We're only
there for like 15 hours. Um, but I bet
on the Super Bowl that what was going to
happen first, either a sack or a
touchdown. The first thing you'd imagine
is a touchdown, not a [__] sack. So,
I lost that bet. The second bet was that
one team would not score three points in
a row and that should hit. So I lost
that bet. And then my other bet was that
each team would score a point in each
half.
So meaning each team would score a point
in each half, first half and then second
half. And that [__] didn't happen
either. So I lost every single bet and
then I went to jail. So, the point was
for those beters to pay for the tickets,
but I took like 3 hours on that [__]
So,
what did you bet on?
Um, I put Chiefs uh Kelsey touchdown and
my coffee touchdown. They both uh Chief
Smack, my coffee smack, but then Kelsey
didn't score a touch a [__]
touchdown.
I put a parlay. It was going to pay out
like it was like plus it was high, bro.
It was a good payout. But [__]
Kelsey, bro.
Yeah, this Super Bowl was trash. That's
why I stre it. [__] was boring. Sorry.
[Music]
Yo. So, thank you, Eric, for [__] me
up. Got you, bro. Always. Appreciate
you, bro. Always. Center for Oh, by by
the way,
cold lunch. So, I have every single hour
out of my day like scheduled out to do
pretty much eat, sleep, naps. Everything
is like in my calendar except for this.
This is the only thing that I am scared
of to do. But it feels good. So, we'll
probably maybe do it later today. I try
to do it maybe like three, four times a
week. So, we just finished the haircut.
It's about 12:40. So, right now is where
I should be waking up from a nap and
then I'd either go straight to eat or
I'll get back on some calls with my team
or like other businesses that I'm
involved in for about 1 to 3 hours where
pretty much I'd finish at around 3:00.
But for today's video, we're going to,
you know, make it more personalized cuz
it just there's not much going on when
I'm just sitting up there in a Zoom
call. So, I'm going to take a quick
shower. We're going to go eat. Pick
which car we're going to take. I don't
know which car we're going to take and
then we're we're going to go see the
boat and other little stuff we have for
the video. So, I'll be back. All right.
So, what car do we take, bro? We take
the Urus wide bodys, my Porsche, my GT3
992 manual or my Lambo twin turbo.
Believe it or not,
what about the Canon?
We're wearing white. It's dirty. We can
take it out tonight. We'll take it out
tonight. What do you want to take?
The Lambo cuz we just got it.
The Lambo?
Yeah, of course. We got to put miles
inside.
All right. We'll come back and then
we'll trade it for the Porsche. All
right.
I heard they check.
So, I don't think you guys understand
how fast this [__] is.
That was good. That was good.
That's the first pull.
Yo, tell me that crazy. I think I've
driven this like six, seven times. Wow.
That does not cuz when it's the first
pull, meaning the first time you floor
it, the turbos are cold, so you don't
get that heat. It's called heat. So, I
click this button right here and then as
soon as I hold it, I can boost lag.
Ready?
Bro, that's just crazy.
[Music]
Yo, I always eat healthy. I don't ever
eat healthy. That's why I didn't even
know what the [__] Five Guys was. Yeah,
I always eat healthy food, but I have to
have my sweet. It's just part of the
process. I have to have my little
chocolate over here.
got a little bowl with some spinach,
chicken, broccoli. But I like eating
healthy whenever you
So buy a Lambo and you don't have to get
normal parking. You can just park it
right here and you could just No one's
no one's going to tell you [__] And
then if you're really ballsy, you don't
put the plate on it. So if even if they
wanted to give you a ticket, they can't.
Oh, and you want to step it up a next
level, you have bags. So it's so low on
the ground, they can't even tow it.
All right. So, look. We just got here
right now. I'mma change real quick and
we're going to wait for Jordan.
Currently 2:20.
2:20. Let's see how long Jordan takes.
You want to go out on the You want to go
like to the boat real quick? All right.
That So, how long will you be at my
house?
Like, not not like it shouldn't take
that long.
250.
30 minutes. 30 minutes later.
A lot of traffic. 30 minutes in Miami
time.
30 minutes later. I said in the video,
if you didn't pull up in 30 minutes, I
was leaving. You pull around. Fine.
Right now, we're on our way to the boat.
Uh, for you guys that don't know, Jordan
is my number one student. So, he's, you
know, turned out to be a student and now
he's part of the family even though he
like doesn't give a [__] anymore about
me.
No, he's talking [__] He's talking
[__] He's talking [__]
You know, he doesn't care about me
anymore. So, whatever. He I taught him
the strategy, became profitable. I say
he doesn't give a [__] anymore. So,
he beat you he beat the winning streak
and that was it.
Yeah. You beat my winning streak and
that's it. You never You've never been
the same. Nah,
never been that same. I had a What was
my winning streak?
Um 14. Yeah. So I had a 14week winning
streak and then what did you go up to?
We got it up to 23.
[Music]
I [__] hate missing gears, bro. So, I
just we just pulled up to marina. I left
the keys in the house. So, I got to go
back to the house, get the [__] keys.
So, we just wasted 35 minute drive for
no reason. So, it's 3:15. We're going to
get traffic back to get the key to then
come back again.
At least we're in the Porsche.
Yeah. At least
we're in the Porsche and we can hit a
little quick.
[Music]
So, what we're going to do right now is
we're just going to do some donuts cuz
we're in traffic and we're just going to
wait for traffic to go down while we're
doing donuts. This is how you drift.
Pull in the clutch. Put it in first. You
rev it to about 5,000. The cars will be
rolling just a little bit. We have it to
about 5 6,000. Then I dump the clutch.
You got it. Got it. See you soon. All
right. Good luck, Jordan.
Yes, sir.
I pray for you.
Have fun.
We'll leave you.
[Music]
Oh, wait. They're right here.
[Applause]
Oh, you are a savage.
That [__] was gangster or what?
Got
home right now. 4 o'clock. So, probably
20 minutes of drifting and stuff. Uh
Jordan has to go. I'm probably going to
take a nap right now cuz it's traffic
hour. We literally can't do anything
right now. Anywhere you go, it's going
to take you 45 minutes to an hour. So,
I'll probably get a quick massage in the
game room and then just take a nap and
around like 6:00 7, we'll go back to the
boat or we'll go out tonight in the can.
So, we'll see. Appreciate you, bro, for
coming. So, this is my game room. um
kind of have a ping pong table. I was
going to do a ping pong table and a pool
table side by side. But then wherever I
put the pool table, it kind of has to
stay there permanently cuz you can't
move it around because of the weight.
And then if I were to put it here, just
hitting a side shot, even have a good
angle. So stood the ping pong table and
massage it. The [__] was like 15,000.
This [__] was fire.
Bro, aren't you like a profitable
trader? You haven't taken zero trades
today.
Yeah, but I took one what, like 3 days
ago and I made 60,000.
I don't show you right now. I took one.
Look, there you go. Look, I'm got to
hide this. But 60,000 on the 13th. And
then if you look at last week's trades,
how much you think I for the week?
50.
Damn. Check it.
130.
Close enough.
That paid for.
That paid for us going to jail while we
streak the Super Bowl. that paid for the
jet, paid for the tickets, and barely
pays the light bill here.
So, just finished right now a Zoom call
with the team. So, I woke up from the
nap about an hour and a half ago. So,
it's currently about 8:30. So, today I
only took a nap for about an hour. So, I
was on my phone for a little bit and we
just finished Zoom call. Now, time for
the gym. All right. So, I don't think
you guys understand how fast this thing
is and how loud this thing is. Probably
as loud as the gears. Sorry neighbors.
[Music]
I wonder what people think like when you
get out the gym and you see that [__]
like who the [__] drives that [__] bro?
But now we're ready. So, I'm feeling a
little sick today. So, we're going to
hit the sauna for longer than usual and
then a little workout probably like
chess. And what I love about this gym is
that it's a private gym and nobody ever
comes here. And uh you know, usually I
can either take my time with machines or
not. So, I haven't been hitting the gym
lately. I'm not going to cap. I can't
lie. But I'm getting back in the grind.
I do sauna every single day. I rather do
this and do cold plunge all day. So,
usually I come in here, it makes me
pretty much like relax, clean out my
pores. Um, and you know, it's good cuz
you kind of sweat it. You're supposed to
hit the sauna when you finish working
out. That's why you're burning fat and
not muscle. Cuz if you do sauna or
cardio before you work out, you're going
to burn muscle. We're not trying to burn
muscle. We're trying to burn fat. But
yeah, I like doing it because it keeps
me accountable and um but I like Yeah, I
like doing it because obviously it's
good for you and it's better feeling
than the cold punch. I'll tell you that
for sure. And honestly, when you get out
of here, you feel amazing. You feel like
you just took a shower. Obviously, you
have to take a shower when you get out
of here, but it feels really good. So,
after here, we're going to go back home.
I have a trade that we might take a
trade. Um but this really kind of how my
days kind of look like. trading in the
morning, meetings, take a nap, go eat,
and then just gym and then more meetings
and more trading. It's kind of boring,
not going to lie. The weekends though,
the weekends, that [__] If you guys
want to see a weekend in the life, in my
life, make sure you guys drop that down
below cuz that right there,
that, my friends, is different. So, just
finished sauna right now. 9:54. So,
little workout, about a 15, 20 minute
workout. So, we're going to go home
right now, shower. While we're
showering, my assistant is going to go
get us some food. And then after we
finish eating, we're going to go check
out the boat because we forgot the key
earlier. So, we're going to go see
what's up with the speakers and then if
anything, just go out and eat a little
bit. So, let's eat. Let's eat. So, food
just got here. Little
about 11:00. So,
usually whenever I eat, I don't watch TV
ever. I'll watch like YouTube videos on
new cars that I'm going to get. So,
we're watching YouTube video right now
on the Cyber Truck. All I'm going to say
is I might get one, but after here, I
have an interview right now, which I
don't know if I'm going to get on with
Fox News because they want to interview
me because of the streaking that I did
in the Super Bowl. And if we don't do
that, then we're just going to go
straight to the boat and then pretty
much prepare for trading London tonight.
So, I'm still trading London, man. So,
we just finished the interview right
now. So, it is 11:35 and we're going to
head to the boat. Why not in the Europe?
So, I've had a lot of dailies in the
past, but there's nothing like this one,
bro. I suck.
This is a truck
pushing like 800 900 horsepower. So, we
just pulled it right now to the marina
where I have my boat. Keep in mind, it's
my first boat. It's not a yacht. It's
not even something big like this. I just
got something to have fun with and it so
I can learn the ocean. I'm a really good
driver in cars, but I want to get the
hang of the water. So, I bought a little
boat just to have fun with, you know,
and the dope part about this place is
that I have access 247 with security
24/7 and I can go out in the boat 24/7.
Like, it's on the water. You guys can
see this is the water right here. So,
don't if this is your first time seeing
my boat, don't laugh at my boat. I like
it. It's fun. All right. It's my first
boat and I'm I'm learning with it. So,
this is sad and forget.
It's a wakeboarding boat. So, I like it
because you can fit like 15 20 people on
it with seats comfortable everywhere and
you can wakeboard, which is dope as
[__] One of my goals this year is to be
able to do a back flip off of me
wakeboarding. So, this is the boat right
here. People that see me out here in the
water in this little ass boat are like,
"Look at this motherfucker." Little do
they know. Little do they know that I
can own all these boats right here. Just
being very humble. Just having fun in a
little boat. What's wrong with that? But
I get bullied out here in the water cuz
this boat's small and out here in Miami,
the normal is like a 100 foot yacht and
they bully you out here. They'll like
push you around like these guys. Oh
[__] I didn't see that. You should have
told me. Yo, so that's Kiki right there.
That's the famous Kiki on the river.
Usually I come here and what this boat
costs I spend it in this club and I pull
up on a yacht and look at us tonight on
the dingy. Look at it. That's the thing.
I've spent there easily
15 20,000 in one night like that without
an issue.
[Music]
So, it's currently 12:30 at night right
now. We might catch this Euro USD sale
in about the next 30 minutes while we're
out here in the water. So, this day in
the life might get extended a little bit
more until tomorrow in the morning cuz
we might catch this trade tonight or we
might also catch this GBPUSD. We might
get in pretty much in the next I'll tell
you right now in the next
uh in the next 30 to 45 minutes we'll be
able to get into this trade. So it's the
power of trading, baby. We can trade
from anywhere in the world. You guys see
all that stuff right there? Those are
all birds. So the birds that are flying
all day, you wonder where they are at
night
right there. Hold on. Hold on. You want
to [__] on my car, [__]
[Music]
Yo, it's crazy. Look at all of them.
Just like that,
you have arrived. Tell me Tell me the
truth, bro. Where else can you [__]
live the life that we live out here in
Miami? Nowhere, bro. Like, from one
second, you could be in the Can-Am in
the woods mudding, having fun. Another,
you could be in a highway racing with a
bunch of Lambos and then you go like
that and you're on the water on a boat.
Like, dude, Miami is a spot for us. This
is why a lot of people here are
successful because from the second you
wake up, you have all of this [__] to
work towards. That's why I'm 23 and I
have it. I picture yacht doesn't have
this right here.
Does that look crooked to you, bro?
I mean, for almost 2 a.m. it looks
straighter and straight.
Yeah, we're good.
And if you notice, the Urus and the
Lambo match the boat. That's not a
coincidence.
[Music]
So, we just got home right now. It's
currently 2 in the morning as you guys
can see up there. So, usually pretty
much trades should pop up anywhere from
now to about 4:00 in the morning. So, I
just chill here for a little bit. Um, as
of right now, I'm looking to sell
EuroUSD, which it's giving us a very
nice sell opportunity here. Pretty much
the same spot where we sold earlier this
week. So, if we lock in another sell, we
pretty much close the week at like I
don't know like 200 250,000. If we can
get a trade GBPUSD, we were going to
enter as well. We simply did not enter.
So, if we don't get any trades by
tonight, I'll update you guys tomorrow
in the morning what we do. So, I just
chill here while I wait for a trade.
Honestly, I just scroll through
Instagram or watch a YouTube video. It's
kind of like my morning. I'm just
focusing time on me and chilling with
the charts. So, let's see what happens
tonight. So, good morning. Currently,
right now it is 9:38 the next day. You
guys can see right here it is Friday,
February 16th, and we ended up getting
into GBPUSD right at 3:00 in the
morning. The trade went right into draw
down the moment that I took it. You guys
can see right here the time stamp 3:00
in the morning down here. It's exactly
when I took it at this left head, right
shoulder, the bearish engulfing
candlestick break in the neckline. And
usually what's supposed to happen is
during London session, it's just
supposed to push the whole way. That did
not happen. It pretty much came back in,
got into a little bit of draw down, but
then now we are up in profit currently.
right now on this trade. We are up about
like $12,000.
So, this is what we're up currently
right now. Um, it's nice. I mean, you
know, I like if I'm not making 50 to
70K, I'm going to love the trade. So,
this trade can probably give me about 40
to 50, so it's like an okay trade. Uh,
so we're going to pretty much hold it
for another 2 to three hours cuz it's
Friday. So, I just caught this quick
trade right before the market closed
just to get something. And if not, I'll
just close like a 20 30k profit because
the market's about to close and I don't
want to hold this trade throughout the
weekend cuz I do believe that it could
come back and then it can retest the
neckline of this left head and
shoulders. So, I believe that it can
strongly retest this head and shoulders
patterns right here. So, it can create a
lower high to then retest the neckline,
retest the EMA to then keep continue
heading to the downside. So, I don't
want to get caught in that drawing
throughout the weekend. So, I'll update
you guys. So, now
I'm going to go back to sleep. That's
it. We're done for like an hour. We'll
take an hour nap.